let questions = [
    {
        "question": "HTML stands for -",

        "option1": "HighText Machine Language",
        "option2": "HyperText and links Markup Language",
        "option3": "HyperText Markup Language",
        "option4": "None of these",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "The correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage is -",

        "option1": "Head, Title, HTML, body",
        "option2": "HTML, Body, Title, Head",
        "option3": "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
        "option4": "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following element is responsible for making the text bold in HTML?",

        "option1": "<pre>",
        "option2": "<a>",
        "option3": "<b>",
        "option4": "<br>",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following tag is used to insert a line-break in HTML?",

        "option1": "<br>",
        "option2": "<a>",
        "option3": "<pre>",
        "option4": "<b>",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "How to create an unordered list (a list with the list items in bullets) in HTML?",

        "option1": "<ul>",
        "option2": "<ol>",
        "option3": "<li>",
        "option4": "<i>",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character is used to represent the closing of a tag in HTML?",


        "option1": "\ (slash",
        "option2": "!",
        "option3": "/",
        "option4": ".",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {

        "question": "How to create an ordered list (a list with the list items in numbers) in HTML?",

        "option1": "<ul>",
        "option2": "<ol>",
        "option3": "<li>",
        "option4": "<i>",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {

        "question": " Which of the following tag is used to define options in a drop-down selection list? ",

        "option1": "<select>",
        "option2": "<list>",
        "option3": "<drop>",
        "option4": "<option>",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following element is responsible for making the text italic in HTML?",
        "option1": "<i>",
        "option2": "<italic>",
        "option3": "<it>",
        "option4": "<pre>",
        "answer": "1"
    },

    {

        "question": "How to add a background color in HTML?",

        "option1": "<marquee bg color: red>",
        "option2": "<marquee bg-color = red>",
        "option3": "<marquee bgcolor = red>",
        "option4": "<marquee color = red>",

        "answer": "3"
    }
];